'Without a Trace' 지난 이야기.
Previously on Without a Trace.
조라는 친구가 있었어요
The guy named Joe.
안젤라를 아주 좋아했죠
Real shine to Angela.
이름이 조 쥬스티였을 거예요
Joe Giusti, I think.
모리스 형사님
특수 요원 존슨입니다
Detective Morris,
Special Agent Johnson.
- 와주셔서 고맙습니다
- 별말씀을요
- Thank you for coming.
- Oh, it's my pleasure.
안젤라를 찾는 데 진척이 있습니까?
Any luck finding a waitress?
아니요, 뭐 아는 것 좀 있으세요?
No. What do you have?
빈민가 지역의 저당 잡힌 집들에서
세 명의 피해자가 발견됐습니다
I've got three other victims found in
foreclosed homes in depressed areas.
조의 가명 하나가
임대인 목록에 있었어요
One of Joe's Aliases popped on a lease.
예상했던 대로 3개월치를
미리 현금으로 지불했더군요
True to form, he paid three months
in advance in cash.
이건 이상한데요
This doesn't add up.
열쇠 구멍을 안쪽으로 해서
자물쇠를 반대로 달아놨어요
That's commercial grade dead bolts
fixated the outside of multiple doors.
돈을 좀 썼어요
Spent some money here.
우발적인 범행이 아니에요
This is too organized.
자막제작 - 네이트 CSI 자막팀
(http://club.nate.com/clubcsi)
딕테이션
이근양(kylee322@hotmail.com)
싱크편집
최자앵(ashaa@nate.com)
한글번역
장주영(jjy715@nate.com)
번역수정
김자현(verve305@nate.com)
한글교정
이미란(lmr0412@nate.com)
이해가 안 가요
Hey, I don't get it.
심장마비로 죽은 건데
왜 이 난리가 난 거죠?
The lady had a heart attack.
How's it make such a mess?
그건, 유리 탁자 위로 쓰러지면서
과다출혈이 됐기 때문이에요
Well, when she, uh, collapsed
she fell on the glass table and bled out.
그렇지 않았다면, 아직 살아있었을 겁니다
Otherwise, she might still be alive.
그럼 난 이 청소비를
지불할 필요가 없었겠네요
And I might not be footing
a bill for the cleanup.
그래도 제가 보기엔
부인이 더 안 된 것 같은데요
It seems to me she's worse off
than you are, sir.
그렇다고, 3천 달러나 해요?
Still, $3000?
출혈량이 많고 튄 곳도 많아요
There's lots of seepage and spray.
다 없애려면 좀 걸려요
Takes a while to get it all.
깨끗이 하지 않으면, 박테리아, 악취도 생기고
혈인성 질병까지도 생길 수 있어요
And if you don't, you can get bacteria,
odors, maybe even blood borne disease.
다음 세입자더러 알아서 하라고 할까요?
You want your next tenant
dealing with that?
어떤 흔적이든 다 없애준다고
보장할 수 있어요?
Can you guarantee me you've
gotten rid of every trace?
아니요, 그런 건 보장할 수 없어요
No. I can never guarantee that.
왜요?
Why not?
전 그냥 치우는 것뿐이니까요
있었던 일을 없었던 걸로는 못합니다
Because I just clean up.
I can't take away what happened.
나 왔어, 여보
Hi, babe.
많이 피곤하지
Hey, you must be exhausted.
오늘은 어땠어?
괜찮았어, 나빴어, 이상했어, 아니면 슬펐어?
How was the job?
Good, bad, weird or sad?
슬픈 일이었어
나이 든 부인이 혼자 돌아가셨어
Sad, I guess.
Old lady died alone.
우리 아기는 어때?
How's she doing?
합창 단원처럼 발차기를 잘해
Kicking like a chorus girl.
해나는 어디 있어?
Where's Hannah?
방에, 중간고사 공부해
In her room, studying for a mid-term.
적어도 5분 전엔 그랬는데 말이지
At least she was five minutes ago.
안녕, 우리 딸
Hi, sweetheart.
- 안녕, 아빠
- 식은 피자 먹는 거야?
- Morning, dad.
- Honey, cold pizza?
냉장고 안쪽에 무지방 요거트 있는데
There's non-fat yogurt
in the back of the fridge.
- 블루베리랑 먹으면 아주 맛있어
- 나 요거트 싫어해
- Goes great with blueberries.
- I hate yogurt.
여보, 별일도 아닌데 그만해
그냥 먹고 싶은 거 먹게 놔둬
Celia, please. It's no big deal.
Let her eat what she wants.
나 싸우러 내려온 거 아니야
I didn't come in here for a world war.
잘 다녀오라고 인사하러 온 거지
I just came in to tell you, mom,
you know, have a good day.
고마워
That's sweet.
사무실이야
It's work.
엄만 그냥 네가 건강했으면 해
Honey, I just want you to be healthy.
나도 알아
I know.
그래
Okay.
빨리 가야겠네
I've got to run.
호텔에서 새 예약 시스템에 관한
교육 실습을 할 거야
The hotel's doing a training workshop
on a new reservation system.
정말 기대돼
So exciting.
안녕 우리 딸
Bye sweetheart.
리오 커틀러 씨랑 18살 된 딸 한나예요
Leo Cutler and his
18-year-old daughter, Hannah.
부인은 트라매인 호텔 사무원이에요
Wife's a desk clerk at the Tramaine Hotel.
집에 와보니 문이 망가진 채로 열려있었고
둘 다 없었답니다
She came home, found the door busted
open and both of them gone.
부인은 지금 어디 있나?
Where's the wife now?
안에요, 엘레나가 만나보기 전에
의사가 진찰 중이에요
Inside, the doctor's checking her out
before Elena talks to her.
임신 4개월째인데
전에 유산한 적이 있어요
She's four months pregnant and has
a history of miscarriage.
- 안에 싸운 흔적은 없고?
- 없어요, 문만 망가졌어요
- Any sign of struggle in there?
- No, just the door.
- 커틀러 씨 직업은 뭐지?
- 범죄현장 청소원이요
- What does Cutler do for a living?
- Crime scene cleanup.
그럼 최근 사건하고
관련이 있을 수도 있겠군
Oh, maybe this is related
to his last case.
- 73세 된 미망인이 심장마비로 죽은 사건인데요
- 아닐 수도 있겠군
- 73-year-old widow died of heart failure.
- Maybe not.
- 이것 좀 보세요
- 뭔가?
- Hi, guys.
- Hey, what's up?
모션 센서 등에서 깨져 나온
유리 조각을 발견했습니다
Found this broken glass from
the motion sensor light
이웃집 뒤편에서요
in the back of the neighbor's houses.
누군가 어두운 걸 좋아했나 본데요
Somebody wanted to keep it dark.
구석에서 재미 좀 보려는 게 아니었다면
Unless that involves foreplay.
절대 좋은 징조가 아니지
It's never good.
Without A Trace
6x02 Clean Up
앤서니 라파글리아(잭 말론 役)
파피 몽고메리(사만다 스패이드 役)
마리앤느 진-밥티스트(비비안 존슨 役)
엔리케 멀셔노(대니 테일러 役)
로슬린 산체스(엘레나 델가도 役)
에릭 클로즈(마틴 피츠제랄드 役)
ORIGINAL AIR DATE ON CBS: 2007/10/04
실종 25시간째
말이 안 돼요
이럴 리 없어요
25 Hours Missing
And it doesn't make any sense,
it's crazy.
뭣 때문에 납치를 해요?
Why would someone take them?
그게 저희가 알아내려는 거예요
That's what we're trying to find out.
잘못 안 걸지도 몰라요
해나 차도 없잖아요
Maybe this is all a mistake.
I mean, Hannah's car is gone.
둘이 같이 어디 갔나 봐요
그럴 수 있잖아요, 그렇죠?
Maybe they went somewhere together.
It's possible, right?
네, 하지만 문이 부서진 거나 등이 깨진 건
설명이 되지 않아요
It is, but... it doesn't explain
the broken door, or the broken lights.
저, 제발 좀 앉아보세요
Now, please, why don't you sit down?
앉아서...
Please...
진정 하세요
Just try to relax.
해나가 해리슨 대 신입생이라고 들었는데요
I hear Hannah is a freshman at Harrison.
전공이 뭐죠?
What does she study?
컴퓨터 공학이요
주간 대학생이에요
Computer Science.
She's a day student.
여기서 함께 살아요
She lives here with us.
- 정말 좋으시겠어요
- 네, 그래요
- That must be very nice for you.
- It is.
딸이랑 같이 있는 시간이 좋아요
I like having her around a lot.
남자친구는 있나요?
Does she have a boyfriend?
데이트를 별로 안 해요
바쁘잖아요
She doesn't really date.
She's very busy, you know?
좋은 아이에요. 정말 착해요
She's good kid, great kid.
요새 커틀러 씨 기분은 어땠죠?
What about your husband's mood lately?
그냥 괜찮았던 것 같아요
말보다는 행동으로 보여주는 사람이에요
It's quiet, I guess.
He's more of a doer than a talker.
평범치 않은 직업을 갖고 계시죠?
And he has an unusual job, huh?
남편은 사람들이 일상생활로
돌아갈 수 있게 돕는 걸 좋아해요
He likes to go in and help
people get back to normal,
사람들도 정말 고마워하고요
and people seem to really appreciate it.
고객하고 문제는 없었나요?
Any problems with clients?
제가 들은 바로는 없어요
Uh, not that he said.
직장 밖에서는요?
What about outside of work?
최근에 마찰이 있던 사람은 전혀 없었나요?
Is there anyone he's had issues
with recently that you know?
요전에 일이 있긴 했어요
Something did happen the other day.
여보, 뭐해?
Hey, what are you doing?
이것 좀 해두려고...
마당 좀 보기 좋게 하는 중이야
I'm just working...
just working on a little curb appeal.
날카로운 연장 쓰면서 술 마시면 안 되지 않아?
You think it's a good idea to mix
sharp tools with, uh, happy hour here?
여보, 임신한 건 정말 기쁜 일이야
You know, honey, the baby
was a beautiful surprise.
해나도 집에 있고 집도 새로 샀고
모든 게 정말 완벽했지
With Hannah home and this new house,
everything was just perfect.
여보, 안 팔아도 돼
내가 몇 시간 더 일할게
Honey, we won't have to sell.
I'll work more hours.
모르겠어
해나 말이 맞을지도 몰라
I don't know.
Maybe Hanna was right.
18년 만에 애를 갖는 건 미친 짓이지
18-year gap between kids is crazy.
Leo, everything’s going to be okay.
여보, 다 잘 될 거야
안으로 들어와
Just come inside.
좀 더 있다 들어갈게
I'll be in in a while, okay?
- 안녕, 우리 딸
- 응
- Hey, Honey.
- Hey.
마음에 드는 거 있어?
See anything you like?
내가 입으면 어떨지 잘 모르겠어
I'm not sure how I'd look
in some of this stuff.
마음 바뀌면 말해, 옷 한 벌 정돈 사줄
비자 카드가 대기하고 있으니까
Well, if you change your mind I've got
a Visa that could probably handle an outfit.
내 일에 신경 끄라고 내가 그랬지!
Hey, remember when I told you
to stay out of my damn business!
그래서요? / 잘 봐둬
네놈 집을 확 불 질러 버릴 테니까
And what'd you do? / Take a look at this
and I'll burn this damn place down.
알아들어?
You hear me?
제가 나갔을 때는
벌써 트럭을 타고 가버렸어요
By the time I got out there,
the man was in his truck driving away.
무슨 일로 싸우는 거였나요?
What was the argument about?
오해가 있었댔어요
Leo said it was a misunderstanding.
그 남자 트럭이 파란색 밴에 긁혔는데
The man's truck was sideswiped
by a blue van,
남편 차를 보고...
and he saw Leo's van, so...
몽타주가 필요한데요, 얼굴 기억나세요?
Can you remember this man well
enough to give us a sketch?
네
I think so.
재미 좀 봤어요?
Having fun?
엄청이요
Oh, loads.
고맙게도 브래들리 포스터가 쥬스티가 증거를 다 닦아 없애기 전에
You got a shooting Bradley Foster
made Giusti leave town
여길 떠나게 한 모양이에요
before he could scrub the place down.
감식반 말로는 여기가 DNA 금광이라는군요
ERT's are saying it's a DNA goldmine.
- 지문은요?
- 어디든지요
- What about prints?
- Everywhere.
쥬스티의 수감 기록 본 적 있으세요?
Now, did you ever look
into Giusti's prison record?
그래이터포드 교도소에서 형을 산 건 알아요
I know he did that stint
at Graterford Correctional.
네, 방을 같이 썼던 콴 리란 사람 아세요?
Yeah. Does a cellmate by the name
of Quan Lee ring a bell?
아니요
No.
필라델피아 경찰한테 붙잡혔을 당시
Well, he was busted by Philadelphia Vice.
대부분 동양인인 12명 정도의 여자들이
They found about a dozen women,
mostly Asian,
안마 시술소 뒷방에 감금돼 있었대요
locked in the back
room of his massage parlor.
그럼 쥬스티가 감방에 있는 동안
인신 매매업을 좀 익혔나 보군요
So Giusti learned a trade
when he was doing time.
그런 것 같아요
Looks like it.
인터폴이 리에 대한 정보를 수집 중이고
저희 쪽에선 수배령을 걸어놨어요
Interpol has a file on Lee.
and we've put stop notices on him.
성과가 있길 바라야죠
So, hopefully we'll catch a break.
인터폴이요?
Interpol?
인력을 좀 더 끌어와야겠군요
We could use some
more manpower on this.
우리 둘이 하기엔 좀 버거울 거 같은데요
Feels a little big for just the two of us.
일단, 감식반이 뭔가 알아내면 알려주세요
그럼 제가 어떻게 해볼게요
Well, send me what ERT finds,
and, uh, I'll see what I can do.
실종 26시간째
26 Hours Missing
난 그 사람한테 아무 짓도 안 했소
내가 뭐 하러요?
I didn't do anything to Cutler.
I mean, why would I?
커틀러 씨가 학대 센터에 신고했던데
이유로 충분해 보이는데요
Well, he called the Abuse Hotline on you
that sounds like a reason.
내 아버지는 골수암으로 돌아가신 거요
My dad died of bone cancer.
그 사람은 방을 치우러 온 거지
경찰한테 거짓말이나 하면 안 되잖아요
He's supposed to disinfect the room,
not lie to the cops.
그럼 아버지 침대에서 발견된
쇠사슬이 달린 볼트에 대해선
So that eyebolt we found in your father's
bedroom with a chain attached,
아는 게 없단 말이요?
you know nothing about that?
그 사람이 심어놨는지도 모르죠
Maybe Cutler planted it.
그럼 침대에서 나온 구더기는요?
How about the maggots we found
in your father's mattress?
커틀러 씨가 그것도 심어놨을까요?
Did he plant those, too?
아버진 주로 침대에 있었어요
Oh, the old man didn't get out much.
좀 더 자주 들릴 걸 그랬어요
I probably should've stopped by more.
아버지 퇴직연금 수표를 가져갈 만큼은
자주 갔던데요
Well, you stopped by often enough
to pick up his retirement checks.
그건 아버지 음식이랑 필요한 걸 사는 데 쓴 거예요
Those were for groceries and stuff.
당신은 아버지를 침실에 묶어놓고
돈을 훔쳐간 거야
You chained your father to the bedroom wall
and stole money from him.
당장은, 유기죄랑 사기죄로
잡아넣기에 부족함이 없지
Right now, I have enough to charge you
with gross negligence and fraud.
또 뭐가 더 있게요
And guess what else.
커틀러 씨 밴에서 당신 지문이 나왔어요
We've got your fingerprints inside his van.
좋아요, 설명하죠
Okay, I can explain that.
이봐, 당신
Hey, man.
뭐 하는 사람이야?
Who the hell do you think you are?
무슨 말씀이죠?
Excuse me?
왠 떨거지 형사가 전화해서
아버지 일을 캐물었다고
Some dirtbag detective just called me
about how I'm treating my dad.
어제 당신이 쓰레기를 운반했는데
You're hauling trash yesterday,
오늘 익명 제보로 경찰한테서
전화가 왔단 말이야
and today the police
are calling from an anonymous tip.
그게 저랑 무슨 상관이죠?
How does that concern me?
저 집에 들어간 유일한
사람이 당신이잖아
You were the only one
inside that house.
그래요
Okay.
내가 신고했소, 그래서 뭐요?
I reported you, so what?
사람이 어떻게 생겼기에
자기 아버질 벽에 묶어 놓는 답니까?
Why don't you tell me, what kind of man
would chain his own father to a wall?
방에 있던 볼트는 페인트칠하려고 박은 거야
That eyebolt was for a painting.
침대 뒤에?
Behind the bed?
바닥에서 30센티나 위에 말이요?
A foot off the floor?
무슨 처분을 받든 당신 몫이요
You deserve whatever you get.
집에서 뭘 또 가져갔어, 어?
What else did you take out
of my house, huh?
날 잡아넣을 증거라도 수집하셨나?
Am I going to find some more
evidence against me in here?
이게 대체 뭐야?
What the hell is this?
- 손 치워!
- 이봐, 진정해
- Get away from those!
- Hey, relax.
네 쓰레기엔 관심 없으니까
I don't want your crap.
내 일에 더 이상 상관 말라고
Just stay the hell out of my business.
며칠 뒤에
경찰이 쳐들어온 걸 보면
Well, I guess he didn't listen to me
because a couple of days later,
내 말을 귀담아듣지 않은 것 같더군요
the cops charged me.
그래서 그 사람 집에 갔던 겁니다
And that's when I went over
to his house.
내 생각을 좀 전달하려던 거예요
Just wanted to give him a piece
of my mind.
짧은 말들이 오갔겠군요
Must've been a short conversation.
메달은 어떻게 생겼던가요?
What did the medals look like?
금이었어요
Gold.
금이요?
Gold?
어...
좀 더 자세히 말해야죠?
Uh...
Little more descriptive?
제대로 보지도 않았어요
Oh, I didn't get a good look at him.
됐어요, 어젠 어디 있었죠?
All right, where were you yesterday?
캔디 걸스에요
Candy Girls.
서쪽에 있는 회원전용 클럽이란 말이요
It's a gentlemen's club on the west side.
어제 온종일 있었어요
확인해 보라고요
I was there all day.
You can check it out.
물론 할 겁니다
Oh, I will.
저 천재 용의자를 확실히 구금해 놓도록 해
Samantha, let's make sure
the criminal genius stays in custody
알리바이 확인하기 전까진
till we can check out his alibi.
네, 어제 캔디 걸스에서 근무한 댄서들이
All right, well, none of the dancers
who worked yesterday
전부 전화를 안 받아요
at Candy Girls are answering
their phones.
그 메달들은 뭘까요?
What do you make of those medals?
나도 모르겠어
운동 경기 기념품일까?
I don't know.
Some kind of sports memorabilia?
돈이 궁했던 건 알고 있잖아
We know he needs money.
직업상 남의 집에 늘 드나들었으니
He's always in other people's homes.
알 수 없지
훔쳤는지도 몰라
I don't know.
Maybe he's stealing.
네
해나랑 친해요
Sure.
Hannah and I are tight.
학교 근처 하이킹 도로에서 만났어요
We met at a hiking trail near school.
그럼, 해나가 하이킹 게시판에
올린 이 글 말인데
So, this post that she put
on the hiking message board
새 연인을 데리고 갈 낭만적인 장소에
대한... 이게 널 얘기하는 거니?
about a romantic spot to
take a new love...is... is that you?
아니요
No.
우린 그냥 친구예요
We're just buddies.
애인이 누구였는지 혹시 아니?
Any idea who it is?
애인은 없는 걸로 알고 있어요
I don't think she's seeing anybody.
제이, 둘이 친하다면서?
Jay, I thought you said
you guys were tight?
네, 같이 웨스턴 시브 밴드를 좋아하는 정도로요. 요원님도 좋아하세요?
Yeah. Tight as in, I just bombed
Western Civ. How about you?
그냥 그런 거예요
You know?
Like that.
너희 사이는 그게 다야?
And that's all it was between you guys?
매일 얘기는 했겠지?
I mean, you guys did talk every day?
요원님이 대학 다녔을 시절엔
그렇고 그런 사이에만 전화를 했나 본데
Maybe back when you were in college,
guys only called girls to get laid.
시대가 바뀌었다고요
Times changed dude.
그래? 그럼 왜 8일 전쯤부터 전화를 안 했지?
Yeah? Why did you stop calling her
eight days ago...
친구?
dude?
전 요즘 남학생 클럽에
들어가려고 노력 중이에요
Look, I'm trying to get
into this fraternity at school.
나중을 위해 인맥을 만들려고요
Lay pipe for the rest of my life.
해나는 수업이 30시간쯤이던가?
우리 둘 다 바빠져서요
And Hannah's carrying 30 hours?
We... we both got busy.
문자 보낼 시간도 없어?
Too busy to send an IM, huh?
해나가 비밀 지켜 달라고 했어요
Hannah made me promise
to keep it quiet.
이런 꼴로 불쑥 찾아와서
협박하는 거요?
Barge into my house with this,
making threats.
- 당신 대체 누구요?
- 그건 알 필요 없고
- Who the hell are you?
- You don't need to know.
- 청소 도구나 챙겨와
- 안 돼요
- Just get your damn stuff.
- No. Forget it.
안 할 거요
내가 바본 줄 알아?
I'm not going to do that. / What you think
I'm going patches, hermane?
선택권 같은 건 없어
Nobody give you a choice.
이 사람도 죽기는 싫었을걸
I don't think he wanted to die, either.
이번이 마지막이라고 전해요
Why don't you tell your people
this is the last time?
우리가 마지막이라고 해야 마지막이야
It's the last time when we say so.
해나? 문 닫아!
Hannah? Shut that door!
그 뒤로는 서로 좀 서먹했어요
Look, Hannah went major emo
on me after that.
얼마간은 제가 전화 안 하길 바랐다고요
She thought I should lose
her number for a while.
무슨 일인지 알아봤다고 말하진 않았어?
Do you know if she, uh,
after her dad about what happened?
그냥 없던 일처럼 하고 지나갔다고 했어요
They... they just pretended
like it never happened.
그때 온 남자가 누군지 알았대?
Did she know who the man was?
아니요
No.
실종 28시간째
28 Hours Missing
총으로 쏴 죽인 녀석이 집에 찾아와서
시체를 치워달라고 한 거잖아요?
That's the shooter comes to Leo's house
and makes him clean up a hit, right?
처음 있는 일이 아니었어
And it wasn't the first time.
네, 그런데 해나가 우연히 들어왔고
전부 본 거예요
All right. Then Hannah stumbles in.
She sees the whole thing.
그래서 범인이 다시 돌아와서
둘 다 데려간 걸까요?
The shooter doubles back,
and... and he takes them both out?
좋아, 이거야, 이거
Okay, I got it, I got it.
같은 날 밤에 말이야
It happened the same night, okay?
커틀러 집에서 아로나 룰스에게
전화를 건 기록이 있어 / 루이즈예요
There was an outgoing call from the Cutler
residence to an Arona Ruls? / Ruiz.
- 루이즈
- 네, 루이즈요
- Ruiz.
- Yeah, Ruiz.
어디 보자, 마약국 경보가 있어요
Let's see. There was a DEA alert.
여기 있네요
아로나 루이즈
All right, here we go.
Arona Ruiz.
한 마약 조직의 중급 운반책이에요
She's a middle level player
in a drug cartel.
살인사건에 연루된 적은?
Any bodies tied to her?
없어요, 기소된 적은 많았지만
형을 산 적은 없어요
No. I see a lot of charges,
but she's never been prosecuted.
- 마약국 경보가 걸려 있단 말이지?
- 네
- And there's a DEA alert on her?
- Yep.
밀고의 냄새가 나는데
Smells like a snitch.
담당자가 만나라고 해서 오긴 했는데
별로 편치는 않네요
My handler suggested this meeting,
but I'm not comfortable.
FBI 본부에서 만나면
더 편했을 텐데요
Maybe you'd be more comfortable
at FBI headquarters.
제가 그 건물에 들어가는 걸 들켰다간
전 죽은 목숨이에요
People see me going
in that building, I'm dead.
그럼 빨리 끝내도록 하죠
Then let's get this over with real quick.
리오 커틀러 씨와 딸을 데려간 게 누구죠?
Who took Leo Cutler and his daughter?
전 전혀 몰라요
I don't have clue.
당신이 그렇게 비협조적인 걸 알면 연방 검사가
Yeah, I don't think the US Attorney's
going to be real happy
별로 기뻐할 것 같지 않은데요
that you weren't more helpful.
오래전 마약 소지혐의라도
다시 기록에 쉽게 올릴 수 있어요
You know, old possession charges can
easily find their way back into the system.
난 내 분야에는 빠삭해요
I know the terms of my deal.
이미 죽은 사람에 대한 혐의는
다시 적용될 수 없을걸요
You can't bring charges back
from the dead.
좋아요, 얼마로 할래요?
All right. How much?
제가 좋아하는 질문이네요
오천이요
My two favorite words.
5.000.
좋아요
얘기해 봐요
All right, fine.
Start talking.
리오가 전에 일을 한번 봐줬어요
Leo worked on job for me.
일하는 걸 지켜보다가
돈이 궁하다는 걸 알게 됐죠
I'd seen him working,
found out he was hard up for cash.
아마 이름이 돌았나 봐요
제가 그 사람을 보낸 게 아니에요
I guess his name got around.
I didn't send him that job.
그럼 누구죠?
Who did?
저도 몰라요, 리오가 며칠 후에 와서는
부탁이 있다고 하더군요
I don't know, but Leo came back at me
a few days later, looking for a favor.
- 스토킹이라도 하는 거예요?
- 두 가지만 말할게요
- What, are you turning into a stalker?
- I'm here for two things.
우선, 내 집으로 다시는
시체 보내지 마세요
First, don't ever send a
body to my house again.
- 딸이 봤단 말이요
- 내가 그런 거 아니에요
- My daughter was there.
- That job didn't come from me.
당신 집 앞에 뭐가 갈지
내가 어떻게 알아요, 또 뭐예요?
I can't control what shows up
on your doorstep. Second?
내가 전에 당신 사정 봐줬으니까
Second, I did your dirty work.
- 이번엔 내 부탁 들어줘요
- 얘기해봐요
- Now, I need a favor.
- I'm listening.
- 처리해야 할 사람이 있어요
- 데이트 상대로요?
- I need someone taken out.
- Like on a date?
그런 게 아니라면
무슨 소리인지 모르겠어요
Cause, otherwise, I don't
know what you're talking about.
왜 이래요
도청장치라도 했을까 봐요?
What the hell.
What, you think I'm wearing a wire?
- 만족해요?
- 네
- You satisfied?
- Yeah.
좋아요, 그럼 이름이라도 대봐요
Good. I need a name.
누가 괴롭히는데 그래요?
Who got under your skin?
가정 문제요
내가 해결해야 해요
It's a family thing.
I got to take care of it.
가정 문제라니
A family thing.
부인한테 가요
영화 하나 빌려서
No. Go home to your wife.
Rent a movie.
나한테 신세 졌잖아요
You owe me.
빚졌다고 할 만한 일은 아니었어요
You don't have what it takes
to put me in you debt.
이봐요, 내가 사람을 좀 볼 줄 아는데
Look, I'm a good judge of people.
해결하려는 문제가 뭐든 간에
Whatever problem this is
you're looking to solve,
이런 식으로 하는 건 당신한테 안 맞아요
this isn't the way for you.
부탁을 안 들어줬더니
가더라고요
I didn't give him what he wanted,
so he left.
집에 찾아온 녀석이 누군지 정말 몰라요?
You sure you don't know who the guy
was that went to Cutler's house?
알론조 산타크루즈 같긴 하네요
뉴어크 외곽에 살아요
Sounds like Alonso Santacruz.
Out of Newark.
그냥 짐작일 뿐이에요
But that's just a guess.
이제 돈 좀 주실래요?
Can I have my money?
영수증에 사인해야 할 거예요
You're going to have to sign a receipt.
- 시간 있어요?
- 그럼, 뭔데?
- You got a minute?
- Sure. What's going on?
조 쥬스티가 감금했던
여자 몇 명 신원을 확인했는데요
I ID'd some of the women
that Joe Giusti held captive in that house.
missing person’s cases,
최소 6명 정도가 현재 실종자 명단에
있는 사람들이에요
At least half a dozen of them are current
아마 더 나올 거 같아요
and I expect to find more.
샐리 올리버, 스파르탄버그, 남부 캐롤라이나 출신
나이는 19세
Sally Oliver, Spartanburg, South Carolina.
Age 19.
실종 7개월째고요
Missing seven months.
제이미 콜린스, 뉴포트 뉴스, 버지니아 출신
23세, 실종 석 달째예요
Jamie Collins, Newport News, Virginia.
Age 23. Missing 3 months.
그래서 내가 뭘 해주면 되는데?
So, what do you want me to do?
제 지휘 하에 전담반을
구성하고 싶어요
I want to set up a task force
under my supervision.
국토안전부에서
Um... you know that Homeland
Security is running point,
테러랑 관련해서 인신매매
전담하는 거 알지
on, uh, human trafficking
if it involves terrorism.
네, 테러랑 관련이 없으면
우선 수사 대상에서 제외되죠
Yeah, and when it's not terrorism,
it's not a priority.
여러 기관에, 여러 관할구를 걸치는
일을 하겠다는 건데
Look, you're talking about a multi-agency,
multi-jurisdictional operation.
- 얼마나 끔찍할지...
- 저도 다 알아요
- I mean, it's a logistical nightmare...
- I understand all that.
그래서 좀 같이 싸워주셨으면 해요
I just need for you to fight for this for me.
좋아, 전화 넣어 놓지
Okay, I'll make some calls.
이건 말도 안 돼요
This is ridiculous.
실종 30시간째
남편이 누굴 죽이려 했을 리 없어요
30 Hours Missing
Leo didn't try to get someone killed.
따님과 관련된 일일지 몰라요
Then perhaps this is about Hannah.
그 애가 왜요?
What about her?
따님이 집으로 들어왔다고 하셨죠
You said that your daughter was sheltered.
남자친구한테 나쁜 일을 당한 게 아닌가 싶어요
I'm thinking maybe she got involved
with a boyfriend that treated her badly.
아니요, 전에 말했듯이
사귀는 사람 없어요
No, I... I told you, she wasn't
involved with anyone.
누군가 상처를 줬어요
Someone hurt her.
- 누구죠?
- 왜 그런 질문을 하세요?
- Who is it?
- Why are you asking me that?
해나에 관한 일이라고 했더니
안색이 변하셨잖아요
Because when I told you this was
about Hannah, I saw you change.
부인, 제 말 좀 들으세요
Mrs. Cutler, you have to listen to me.
모든 사람이 여기 와서는
뭔가를 숨겨요
People come here all the time,
and they keep things from us.
or they think it doesn’t matter.
당황하거나 부끄러워하거나
중요하지 않은 일이라고 생각하죠
They get embarrassed or ashamed,
하지만, 모든 게 중요해요, 아시겠어요?
모두 다요
Well, everything matters, okay?
Everything.
왜 깼는지는 모르겠지만
I don't know what woke me,
이, 삼일 전 밤에...
but a couple of nights ago...
아빠 못 믿겠어
약속했잖아
I can't believe you.
You promised.
- 도와주려는 거야
- 도움 필요 없다니까
- I'm going to help you.
- I don't want your help.
아빠, 그만해
빨리 나가
No, dad, just stop it.
No. Now I want you to leave.
들어봐, 난 널 도우려는 거야
Honey, listen, I want to help you.
아빠 도움 필요 없어
내가 아빨 믿다니 미쳤지
I don't want your help.
I made a mistake ever trusting you.
아빠 그거 알아?
And you know what else?
아무리 내가 특별하다는 메달 같은 거
만들어줘도 그건 진짜가 아니야
Giving me a medal that says
I'm special doesn't make it true.
- 사랑한다
- 나 그냥 내버려둬
- I love you.
- Just stay away from me.
- 얘야, 제발
- 나 좀 내버려둬!
- Please, honey.
- Just stay out!
여보, 왜 그래?
Leo, what's going on?
해나랑 얘기해봤는데
I talked to Hannah.
무슨 일인지 말을 안 하더군요
She wouldn't tell me
what was going on...
그래서 억지로 시켰는데
so I pushed her.
혹시 아빠가 그런...
I asked her if her dad had, you know...
해나 말이, 절대 그건 아니랬어요
She said, absolutely not.
남편 분은 뭐라고 하던가요?
What did Leo say?
학교에 뚱뚱한 사람 놀리는 걸
좋아하는 선생이 있다면서
Hannah had a teacher
who thought fat jokes were funny.
남편은 뭔가 적극적으로 대응하고 싶은데
해나가 그냥 놔두라고 했대요
Leo wanted to confront him.
Hannah said to just let it go.
그 말을 믿으셨어요?
Um, did you believe his story?
저도 남편이 마약상들 뒤 봐주는 건 알아요
좋게 보일 리 없죠
I know with Leo cleaning up
for those drug people, it doesn't look good,
그렇지만 절대로 딸한테 상처 줄 사람이 아니에요
but he would never harm our daughter.
해나가 말한 메달은 뭐죠?
What about those medals
Hannah mentioned?
10년 전, 3학년 운동회날 처음으로 줬었죠
He gave her first one ten years ago
after a third grade field day.
해나가 아무 경기에도 못 이겨서
She didn't win anything.
많이 실망했는데...
She felt really bad, so...
남편이 메달을 만들어줬어요
Leo made her a medal.
"힘내"라고 쓰여 있었죠
It said, "Best Foot Forward."
둘 만의 이벤트가 됐어요
It became their thing.
하이킹 갈 때나, 성적을 받았을 때, 기분이 안 좋은 날에 기운 나게 해줬죠
For hikes, for grades, to cheer her up
if she was having a bad day.
밴 안에 다른 쓰레기랑 함께
버려진 걸 남편 분이 발견하셨어요
Leo found them tossed out
with the rest of the trash in the van.
해나는 그 메달을 정말 좋아했어요
버렸을 리가 없어요
Hannah loved those medals.
She would never throw them away.
제발
Please.
둘을 찾아주신다고
약속해주세요
You have to promise me
you'll help me find them.
두 사람 다요
The two of them.
제 인생 전부예요
They're my whole life.
자네 생각은 어때?
What's your gut?
딸을 보호하기 위해 살아가는 아버지 같아요
I think this is a father who spent
his entire life protecting his daughter.
딸이 자신감을 느끼도록 도와주고요
Help her to feel good about herself.
백만 년이 가도 아버지가
딸을 해칠 것 같진 않아요
I don't see him hurting her
in a million years.
트래버스 주립 공원에서
해나 차를 찾았어요
Guys, we found Hannah's car inside
of Travers State Park.
실종 32시간째
32 Hours Missing
둔기에 의한 외상이
가장 유력한 사인이에요
Blunt-force trauma is most
likely the cause of death.
현장에 있는 혈흔으로 봐서,
Based on blood loss at the scene,
다른 장소에서 살해된 다음
여기로 옮겨진 것 같대요
the MD thinks she was killed
somewhere else and then moved here.
사망 추정 시각은?
Estimate of time of death?
아직 몰라요
No, it's too soon to say.
그래 그럼 계속 상황 알려줘
Okay.
Keep me posted.
네
All right, bye.
해나 주머니에서 이걸
찾았는데
We, uh, found this
in one of Hannah's pockets.
두꺼운 종이나 하드 보드지 같아
It's a some kind of heavy paper
or cardboard.
- 감식반에 넘길게
- 그래
- I'm gonna run it over to forensics.
- Okay.
그럼 나중에 봐
All right? See ya.
부인은 1번 방에 와 있어요
The mother's in Interview One.
좋아, 우리 둘 중 하나가
말해줘야 할 텐데
Okay, well, one of us
has got to tell her.
그렇죠
I know.
난 괜찮은데
내가 할까?
I don't mind doing it.
Do you want me to do it?
이런 얘길 모르는 사람한테서
듣게 할 순 없어요. 제가 할게요
She shouldn't hear this from
a stranger, so I'll do it.
그래
Okay.
안 돼, 안 돼!
No, no!
아니야, 아니야
No, no, no.
안 돼
No.
그 종이는 어떤 바에서
나온 잔 받침이에요
That paper thing it was
a table display from a bar.
주머니에 집어넣고서는
그냥 빨았나 봐요
She probably stuck it in her pocket,
then it went through the wash.
그런 적 있으시죠
You've done that.
맞다, 빨래 안 하죠
Right. You don't wash suits.
감식반에서 가습기로 부풀렸다가
Anyway, forensics plumped it up
in their humidifier,
연구실 오븐에서 건조했더니
짜잔
air dried it in their Easy-Bake,
and voila.
- 저게 다야?
- 잠깐만 있어 봐요
- That's it?
- Give me a sec.
프로그램이 잉크 흔적을 읽어들여서
The program reads trace elements
of the ink,
장난감 그림판처럼 빈 곳을 메우는 거예요
fills it in like an Etch-A-Sketch.
감식반이 알아낸 바로는,
All right, according to forensics,
해나 주변에 난 부츠 발자국이
the boot prints found around
Hannah's body belong to a make,
75에서 85킬로그램 사이,
신장이 155에서 175 사이인 남자래
175 to 190lb,
five nine to five eleven.
커틀러 씨가 키 155에 75킬로그램이야
Leo was five ten and 175 pounds.
아버지가 죽인 걸 알아내는데
시간을 더 들여야 하는 걸까?
Could we take a little longer getting
to a father killing his own child?
글쎄, 그럴 수도 있겠지만 부인 말론
시신이 발견된 장소가
Well, we could, but Mrs. Cutler
says where we found the body
두 사람이 가장 좋아하는
하이킹 장소랬어
was Hannah and Leo's
favorite hiking spot.
여기 뭐 나온 것 같아요
Well, guys, I think I got something.
그림이에요
It's a drawing.
"당신 때문에 차를 멈췄어요"
"You stop traffic."
저런 말에 여자들이 넘어가긴 하는 거야?
Does a pick-up line
like that ever work?
조사해보시면 알게 되겠죠
Guess you'll find out.
여기 이 그림 그린
바 이름이 있어요
Here's the name of the bar
where he drew it.
누군지 알겠어요?
Do you recognize her?
수없이 많은 여자들이 왔다 가요
A lot of girls come through here.
게다가 내 부츠에 5달러를 찔러주지는
않으니까요
They're not the ones putting
a five in my boot.
그림을 그려준 남자랑 같이 왔었을 거예요
She might have been with a guy
who was drawing her a picture.
아, 그 뚱뚱한 애
Oh, yeah, the chubbette.
이상했죠 같이 있던 남자애들이
그 애랑 어울릴 만한 부류가 아니었거든요
It was weird, the guy she was
with was totally out of her league.
어쨌든, 펜을 빌려줬어요
Anyway, he borrowed my pen.
네가 정말 나랑 통계 수업 같이 들었어?
So you were really in my stats class?
네 뒤에 앉았었어
I sat behind you.
그걸 몰랐다니
What a waste.
타임머신 타고 다시 돌아가야겠다
Come on, let's get a time
machine and go back.
그래
Yeah, right.
여기 감사해야 할 사람이 오는구만
Now here's to the guy
I should be thanking.
해나를 알아볼 기회를 준
제이를 위해
To Jay for finally giving me
the Hannah-vision goggles.
- 관둬
- 고마워, 제이
- Cut it out, man.
- Thanks, Jay.
물론
Sure, no problem.
내가 이해가 안 되는 건
왜 이렇게 늦게 소개해줬느냐는 거야
The only thing I don't understand
is what took you so long to introduce us.
너 해나 좋아하지, 그렇지?
I mean, you have the hots for her, right?
뭐? 정말?
What? You do?
말해 봐
Come on, tell her.
지금이 고백할 기회야
This is your moment.
션이 장난치는 거야
Sean's just messing around.
그래, 내가 재밌으라고
제이 괴롭히는 거야
Yeah, I'm just, I'm having
a little fun with old Jay.
우리가 즐길 재미에
비하면 아무것도 아니지만
But... not as much fun
as we're gong to have.
- 이름이 제이였다고요?
- 네
- He said his name was Jay?
- Yeah.
이 남잔가요?
That him?
네 그 꼽사리 친구 맞아요
Yeah, that's the third wheel.
좋아요, 고마웠어요
All right, thank you.
제이, 다 말한 게 아니더구나
Jay, you didn't tell us the whole story.
해나 집에 찾아온 살인범
이야기해드렸잖아요
I told you about the hit men
that came to their house.
해나가 네 친구를
좋아했단 말은 안 했잖아
You didn't tell us that Hannah
had a crush on your friend.
제가 잊었었나 봐요
I... I guess I forgot.
대체 문제가 뭐야?
What's the matter?
뚱뚱한 애를 좋아해서
부끄럽니? / 아니요
You embarrassed that you
like a fat girl? / No.
그럼 그 뚱뚱한 여자앨 좋아했단 말이지?
So you do like the fat girl?
그럼 네가 이기는 게임이었겠네
해나는 뚱뚱하니까 그렇지?
Well, that means your odds are
pretty good because she's fat, right?
- 해나한테는 선택권이 없잖아
- 아뇨, 그런 거 아니었어요
- So her options are limited.
- No, it wasn't like that.
그럼 어떤 건데? 뚱뚱한 여자앨 좋아한 것도
아니고 안 좋아한 것도 아니고...
So how is it? Either you like the fat girl
or you don't like...
- 그런 식으로 말하지 마세요
- 도대체 무슨 짓을 한 거야?
- Stop talking like that.
- What did you do to her?
그냥 얘기했어요
I talked to her.
같이 어울리고, 잘 대해줬어요
We hung out, I... I treated her nice.
정말로 좋아했다고요
I really liked her.
바에서 우연히 션을 만났는데
We ran into Sean at the bar and...
해나가 션을 좋아하는 걸 보고
화가 났어요
when I saw she liked Sean,
I got really upset.
션은 해나라는 애가 있는지도 몰랐어요
He never even know she existed.
션이 여자들은 다 나쁜 년이랬어요
Sean said women were bitches.
본때를 보여줘야 한다고요
We should teach her a lesson.
일이 그렇게까지 될 줄은
정말 몰랐어요
I had no idea it was going
to turn out so bad.
걱정 마
내가 알아서 할게
It's okay.
I know what I'm doing.
넌 경험이 많을 테니까
You've probably done this a lot.
아니, 내 말은
No, I... I just...
그러니까
I just meant...
날 믿어
trust me.
즐겁게 해줄게
You're going to have a great time.
널 믿어
I knew you'd be great.
아직 신호 안 왔냐?
Did he give the signal yet?
빨리, 션
실망시키지 마
Come on, Seany,
don't let us down.
빨리
Come on.
해나, 넌 정말 아름다워
Oh, Hannah, you're so beautiful.
왔다
That's it.
버텨!
Hold on!
암소를 타야지!
Ride the cow!
- 제발 그만해, 잘못했어
- 암소를 타자!
- Please stop. I'm sorry.
- Ride that cow!
12초 ...14, 15
12... and 14, 15.
제발
Please.
최대한 오래
The goal was to, um...
해나를 누르는 게
목적이었어요
to ride her,
as long as possible.
션은 그걸 로데오라고 불렀죠
Sean called it rodeo.
얼마 동안 그러고 있었니?
How long before you let her go?
아마 1분 정도였을 거예요
Maybe a minute.
해나는 옷을 집어들고
뛰쳐나갔어요
She just, uh, she grabbed
her clothes and ran out.
뒤따라갔니?
And did you go after her?
그러고 싶었어요
I wanted to.
얼마나 미안한지 말하고 싶었어요
I wanted to tell her how sorry I was.
해나 아버지가 아신 것 같았어요
Her dad must have found out
저한테 와서 션 주소를 물어봤거든요
because he came to me
and he wanted Sean's address.
알려드렸니?
Did you give it to him?
네
Yeah.
이렇게 되길 바란 게 정말 아니었어요
I never wanted any of this to happen.
제발 해나를 찾으면 제가 많이
미안해한다고 전해주세요
Will you please, when you find
Hannah, tell her how sorry I am?
제이...
Jay...
해나는 죽었어
Hannah's dead.
해나가 그 일로 맘 상했다면
유감이에요
Look, I'm, I'm sorry
if Hannah was upset by what happened.
그렇지만, 아시잖아요
But, you know how it is.
남자애들이 한창때 다 그렇죠
미친 짓도 하고요
A bunch of guys in their prime,
it gets crazy.
그리고..저 해나 좋아했어요
And... I liked Hannah.
아주 즐거운 시간을 선사하려고 했어요
I wanted to show her a real nice time.
너한텐 강간의 정의가
"아주 즐거운 시간"이니?
Is rape your definition
of "a real nice time"?
해나도 전적으로 동의했어요
She totally consented.
해나가...
Did she consent...
소 방울 소리로 놀림당하면서 붙잡혀서
to cowbells and being restrained
소리 지르고 시간을 재는 남자애들한테
둘러싸이는 데도 동의했니?
and having a bunch of guys standing
around yelling while they were timing it?
거기에도 동의했니?
She consented to that?
해피엔딩이 법적 의무는 아니잖아요
I didn't think a happy ending
was a legal requirement.
해나 아버지가 네가 한 짓 때문에
널 찾아갔어
Her father came looking for you
because of what you did,
그래서 지금 아버지는 실종이고 해나는 죽었어
and now he's missing and she's dead
넌 꼼짝없이 걸렸어
and you're in this up to your neck.
이제 그만 말하고
아버지한테 전화해야겠네요
I think I'd better stop talking
and call my dad.
검사세요
He's an attorney.
물론 그렇지
Of course he is.
훌륭하군
Perfect.
들어봐
Tell you what.
빨리 아빠한테 전화하지그래
Why don't you call your daddy?
아버지가 해결해 주시겠지
I'm sure he'll fix it.
우리 요원더러 전화를 갖다주라고 하지
I'll have an agent bring you a phone.
해나 살해 용의로 붙잡을 수가 없어요
그냥 풀려날 거예요
We can't tie him to Hannah's body.
He's going to walk.
자넨 지휘 본부로 돌아가
You should go back
to the command post.
- 무슨 계획 있으세요?
- 별로 알고 싶지 않을걸
- What are you planning?
- You don't want to know.
당연히 알고 싶죠, 도와드릴게요
Yes, I do, maybe I can help you.
- 돕겠다고?
- 네
- You want to help?
- Yeah.
좋아, 저 녀석한테 커피나 물, 소다
뭐든지 최대한 많이 갖다줘
Okay, I want you to ply him with
as much coffee, water, soda as possible,
그랬다가 화장실에 가면
나한테 전화해
and when he needs to go to
the bathroom, you call me.
여자를 그렇게 막 대하는 너 같은 애들은
뭐가 문제인 거냐?
What is it with guys like you
who like to treat women like crap?
응?
Huh?
뭐였어?
What was it?
"엄마가 날 사랑하지 않아요"
"My mommy didn't love me."
"아빠는 날 학대했어요"
"My daddy kicked my ass."
아니면 그냥 여자를 괴롭히는 게 좋은 거야?
Or do you just simply
enjoy humiliating women?
뭐야?
뭐가 문제야?
So what is?
What's the, what's the problem?
전 아무 문제없어요
I don't have a problem.
힘없는 여자애들 때리는 게 좋아?
그래?
You like to hit little girls?
Yeah, huh?
- 이러면 안 되는 거 아니에요
- 벌써 했잖아
- You can't do this.
- I just did.
알았어요, 알았다고요
Okay, okay. Okay, okay.
부는 게 좋을 거야 아니면 다시
처넣을 테니까
You'd better talk, you little..
or I'm gonna drag you back in there!
싫어요, 알았어요, 말할게요
No, no, no, okay, okay, listen, listen.
아까 말한 대로 해나 아버지가 찾아왔었어요
He came after me just like you said
뭐 하는 거예요?
What the hell you doing?
널 기다렸지, 션
Waiting for you, Sean.
저 아세요?
Do, I, uh...
Do I know you?
네가 내 딸을 알지
You know my daughter.
해나
Hannah.
네가 무슨 짓을 했는지 알아?
You know what you did to her?
- 아느냐고
- 설명할게요
- You know what you did?
- Please, I can explain.
설명?
설명을 한다고?
Can explain it?
You can explain it to me?
- 오
- 내 딸을 어떻게 망쳤는지 설명하겠다고?
- Oh... okay.
- Explain how you ruined my baby?
- 네가 망쳤어
- 알았어요 죄송해요, 네?
- You ruined her!
- No, okay, I'm sorry. Okay?
너 같은 게 아직도 살아있어야 해?
Why the hell are you still alive?
Please don’t' shoot me.
제발 쏘지 마세요
쏘지 마세요, 죽이지 마세요
Don't shoot me. Don't kill me.
제발요, 네
제발, 오 하느님
Please don't, okay?
Okay, oh, God. Oh, God, no.
그리곤 총을 집어서
나갔어요
The he just, he just picked up the gun
and he, and he left.
널 그냥 뒀을 리가 없어
There is no way that
he would let you walk.
커틀러 씨한테 무슨 짓을 했어?
Now what did you do with Leo?
숨 막혀요
숨 막힌다고요. 그만해요
You're chocking me,
you're chocking me. Stop, stop.
그래, 네 목을 부러뜨려볼까 하는 중이야
Yeah, I'm working my way up
to breaking your neck.
안 돼요, 알았어요
말해요
Stop, stop, stop, stop, okay, listen.
Listen, okay, okay,
총을 내려놓더니
he put down the gun
절 협박했어요
and, and, and, he threatened me.
내 손으로 하진 않겠어
I'm not gonna do it.
내 딸을 너무 사랑하니까
I love my daughter too much.
경찰에 신고하겠어
I'll let the police deal with you.
감옥에서 얼마나 잘 버티는지 보자
See how tough you are in prison.
그러고 나서 차에 싣고
And then, I... I, I, I loaded him
into the car
인적 없는 주차장에
버렸어요
and I, I , I dumped him
in an abandoned lot.
어디야?
Where?
트래비스 가랑 해밀턴 가 사이요
Travis and Hamilton.
바로 옆에 마약 밀거래소가 있어요
There's a, there's a crack house
next door.
잘했어
이제 앉아
Good boy.
Take a seat.
여기야
Over here.
내가 보고 있을게요
빨리 응급 구조원이요
I've got him.
Get EMT quick.
커틀러 씨, 델가도 요원입니다
어디를 다치셨어요?
Hey, Leo, this is Agent Delgado.
Where are you hurt?
배요
Stomach.
구조원이 오고 있어요, 괜찮으실 거예요
Help is coming, you'll be fine.
커틀러 씨?
Mr. Cutler?
션을 따님의 강간범으로 잡아넣을 증거는 충분합니다
We have more than enough evidence
to convict Sean of your daughter's rape.
커틀러 씨께 총을 쏜 것도 포함해서요
And of your shooting.
그런데 몇 가지 풀리지 않은
But there are some unresolved questions...
의문이 있어요
about your daughter.
네, 그러시겠죠
Yes, of course.
폭스 런 하이킹 도로 밑에서
시신을 발견했는데요
She was found at the bottom
of the Fox Run Trail.
그 길에 아주 좋은 지점이 있어요
There was a spot on the trail...
날이 맑으면
3킬로미터 밖까지 보이죠
where on a clear day,
you could see for almost two miles.
네, 압니다. 부인께서 말씀하시더군요
I know, your wife told,
따님이 제일 좋아하는 곳이었다고요
told us that that was your
daughter's favorite place.
아무리 여러 번 하이킹을 가도
No matter how many times we hiked it,
언제나 놀라워했어요
she always acted surprised.
언제나 전망을 보고 감탄했었죠
She was always surprised by the view.
시신을 버릴만한 장소는 아니죠
It's an unlikely place
for someone to dump her body.
게다가 아주 얌전히 놓여있었어요
And the way we found her,
perfectly placed.
누군가 아주 정성스럽게...
It looked like someone
took a lot of care...
눕혀 놓은 거였어요
putting her there.
쓰레기통에 메달이 있는 걸 보고
무슨 일이 생긴 걸 알았어요
When I found the medals in the trash,
I knew something had happened to her.
억지로 말하게 했더니
I forced her to tell me and...
아기를 생각해서 엄마한테 말하지 말랬어요
she made me swear not to tell her mother
for the baby's sake.
얘야, 들어봐
Honey. Honey, honey, listen.
그래 네 말이 맞아
네가 원하는 대로 하렴
I decided that you were right.
It's up to you how to handle this.
경찰, 치료사
네가 원하는 대로 해
Police, therapy.
Whatever you want.
아빠, 됐어요 / 네가 하자는 대로 할게
잠깐만
Dad, no. / I'll follow your lead.
Wait, sweetheart.
네가 나한테 화난 거 알아
I know you were angry
with me the other night
아빠 방식을 강요해서
for telling you what you should do.
하지만, 아빠는 네가 상처받은걸
참을 수가 없었어
But, I... I just couldn't bear
how he made you feel.
괜찮아요, 아빠
정말이에요
It's okay, dad.
Really, it is.
정말이니?
You sure?
네
Yeah.
지금 제가 원하는 게 뭔지 아세요?
Right now you know what I want?
말만 해
Name it.
체리 코크하고
6인치짜리 대형 샌드위치요
I want a Cherry Coke
and a six inch grinder.
칠면조하고 다 넣어서요
Turkey with everything.
양파도?
Even onions?
네, 양파도요
Yeah, onions, too.
그래, 30분 안으로 갔다 올게
Okay. I'll be back in
less than 30 minutes.
서둘지 마세요
No rush.
사랑해요, 아빠
I love you, dad.
나도 사랑한다, 우리 딸
I love you, too, sweetheart.
해나?
Hannah?
해나, 이거 와서 풀어줘
Hannah, come take the chain
off the door.
한...
Han...
해나?
Hannah?
얘야?
Sweetie?
저 예뻐요?
Do I look pretty?
오, 하느님
왜 이러니?
Oh. Oh, God, baby,
what are you doing?
빨리 가자, 가서 약을 다 빼내야 해
Come on, we gotta get
those pills out of you.
싫어요, 내버려두세요
No, no, let go of me.
얘야
다 좋아질 거야, 약속해
Listen, sweetheart,
I'm gonna make it better. Promise.
아니야! 아직도 몰라
게네들 말이 다 맞아
No! Don't you get it.
All of them were right.
난 뚱뚱하고 끔찍한 돼지야!
I'm a fat, horrible pig!
얘야, 그렇게 말하지 마
Sweetheart, don't say that
about yourself.
내버려둬요
Let me go.
내 귀여운 딸이었어요
She was my little girl.
피가 너무 많이 나와서
There was so much blood.
네, 압니다
I know.
치우셨어요?
You cleaned up?
딸애를 숲에 데려다 주는 게...
I thought if I put her in the woods...
애 엄마가 그걸 보게 할 순 없었어요
I, I couldn't let her mother find her like that.
부인한테 말하셔야 할 것 같습니다
I think you need to tell your wife that.
들어오라고 해주시겠어요?
Could you ask her
to come in here, please?
네, 물론입니다
Yes, of course.
자막제작 - 네이트 CSI 자막팀
(http://club.nate.com/clubcsi)